## **UHOOD AL MAZROUEI**

MEDIA SPECIALIST PHOTOGRPHER VIDEOGRAPHER

#### **OBJECTIVE**

A professional with 15+ years of experience in the field of Information Technology and Communications with in-depth experience in Project Management. I am seeking a job that will strengthen my personal development and establish my innovative approaches in the field of Communications and Media.

#### **EDUCATIONAL HISTORY**

#### **Higher Colleges of Technology**

Bachelor of Information Management | 2008 - 2010

Awarded by the Mother of Nation, Her Highness Sheikha Fatima Bint Mubarak for graduating the Bachelor's degree with Distinction.

#### **Higher Colleges of Technology**

Higher Diploma in Business Information Technology 2000 - 2004

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

- ITIL® Foundation.
- ITIL® Operational Support and Analysis Attendance.
- ISO 20000.
- Innovation in the Government.
- PMP Course.
- Artificial Intelligence Course.
- Information Design Basics.
- Critical Thinking
- IT Service Management Case Experience
- Enterprise Project Management (EPM).
- RedHat Administration.
- IELTS score 6.5.
- Digital Marketing Manage Paid Digital Campaigns
- First Aid Training.

#### **CONTACT ME AT**

052 688 1777

◆ Dubai, United Arab Emirates

### PERSONAL BACKGROUND

Nationality: Emirati Gender: Female

Languages: Arabic - English - Spanish

## **AWARDS RECEIVED**

- Received an Innovation Award for creating the Innovation Website for Emirates Post Group.
- Awarded by the CEO of Emirates Post for producing two Motion Graphic Videos and running the Leadership Ceremony.
- Awarded as one of the Best Employees in the IT department of Emirates Post.
- Awarded by The Dubai Customs
   Director General for planning,
   designing, and creating a promotional
   video for the Reform and
   Modernization Program.
- Reform & Modernization Program Contributor of the Month for February and July. Awarded by the Director General of Dubai Customs.
- Won the 1st prize for a photography competition in the Higher Colleges of Technology.
- Won a Prize for directing and shooting a video commercial for a Coffee Shop.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Content Creator (Videographer/Photographer)

#### Freelancer | March 2020 to Present

- Professional Videographer, Photographer, and Editor.
- Expert in using Videography and Photography equipment.
- Expert at Color Grading in Final Cut Pro and Davinci Resolve.
- Photographed his Highness Sheikh Nahyan bin Mubarak Al Nahyan, Minister of Tolerance at Expo 2020, The content was shared with The Ministry of Tolerance.
- Photographed Her Excellency Hessa bint Essa Buhumaid, Minister of Community Development at Expo 2020.
- Attended Expo 2020 as an Invitee for the International Public Speaker Ms. Shereen Mitwalli to film and document Mother's Day event.
- Filmed The International Tourism Forum.
- · Attend Invites for Events to create content for clients.
- Expert in Retouching and editing photos in Adobe Photoshop.
- Working with different brands to create Social Media content for their accounts.
- Create Social Media Marketing Campaigns.
- Analyzing the digital marketing plan and social media strategy and identifying strategic weaknesses and making recommendations for improvements.
- Write Social Media content in Arabic and English.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- Operating Systems: Apple (macOS), Microsoft Windows, and Linux.
- Designer & Multimedia Tools: Adobe After Effects, Premier, Photoshop, Illustrator, Final Cut Pro, Davinci Resolve, and Spline 3D Designer.
- Microsoft: Visual Studio, SharePoint, and expert in Microsoft Office.
- Oracle Applications 12 c. HTML, CSS, ASP, ASP.NET, C#, PHP, JavaScript, and XML.
- BMC Remedy, Qlikview, Joomla.

#### INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

- The ability of communicating in Arabic, English and Spanish.
- The ability to work in teams co-operatively and individually.
- Time management and organizational skills.
- Innovative thinking and creativity.
- · Always up-to-date about technology.
- Fast independent learner and I have flexibility, open-mindedness and attention to details.

### **Emirates Post Group - IT Department**

# Senior Team Leader - Oracle ERP & Change Manager Deputy Director of ERP Systems | March 2016 to March 2020

- Accountable for the successful delivery of all project phases, releases, and project components for Procurement, Inventory, Human Resources, Self Service, and Payroll modules of the ERP.
- Responsible for overall quality, engagement, and adherence to the schedule of the project.
- Providing support for various Functional & Technical requirements of HR, Payroll, and Procurement Modules.
- Support HR, Procurement Modules of ERP applications, and user issues.
- Ensure seamless interfacing with various systems.
- Complete responsibility for user setup and configuration.
- Create detailed systems documentation, test scripts, and presentations.
- Implement/Train users on new functionalities.
- · Incident Management.
- Follow the Change Management process for all the Change Requests.
- Quality checks all the Documentations (Business Requirements Document, User Acceptance Test Document, and Post Implementation Reviews).

#### Webmaster & Change Manager March 2009 to March 2016

- Change Manager. Manage all change requests on BMC Remedy.
- Manage Emirates Post External and Internal Websites.
- Troubleshoot any issues related to the websites.
- Plan and develop new websites.
- Monitor all the web servers.
- Manage all complaints and inquiries related to eServices on Sage CRM.

### **Dubai Customs - Development Division**

#### Communications Executive Apr 2006 to Feb 2009

- Maintaining the Internal Website
- Editor and Photographer.
- Developing, planning, and managing the implementation of the Communication Strategy.
- Manage all media-related and communication plan.

## Other Work Experience

Abu Dhabi Islamic Bank - Stocks Registration Officer August 2005 to October 2005 Dubai Transport - IT Website Developer January 2004 to March 2004